Hennepin County
Minnesota Historical Society
Marriage, birth, and death records.
1853-1996.
Minnesota Historical Society
Hennepin County (Minn.).
Marriage certificates (1853-1996) and index (1853-1989), birth certificates (1866-1902) and index (ca. 1870-1931), and death certificates (1870-1909) and index (1890-1931).
6.0 cu. ft. (467 microfilm reels).
ARRANGEMENT
The records are arranged in the following sections:
Marriage Certificate Index, 1853-1989 (SAM 447-I, 31 reels)
Marriage Certificates, 1853-1996 (SAM 447, 366 reels)
Birth Certificate Index, ca. 1870-1931 (SAM 448-I, 2 reels)
Birth Certificates, 1866-1902 (SAM 448, 50 reels)
Death Certificate Index, 1890-1931 (SAM 449-I, 1 reel)
Death Certificates, 1870-1909 (SAM 449, 47 reels)
CATALOG HEADINGS
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the catalog of the Minnesota Historical Society. Researchers desiring materials about related topics should search the catalog using these headings.
Topics:
Marriages -- Minnesota -- Hennepin County.; Vital statistics -- Minnesota -- Hennepin County.
Document Types:
Birth records.; Death records.; Marriage records.; Microforms.
ADMINISTRATIVE INFORMATION
Location of Originals:
Location of originals is unknown; presumed to have been destroyed following microfilming.
Provenance:
Film received from Hennepin County Taxpayer Services, June 2009.
Accession Information:
Accession number: 2011-1
DETAILED DESCRIPTION OF THE RECORDS
- Marriage Certificate Index, 1853-1989
  Alphabetical listing by male and female surnames, along with corresponding marriage certificate volume and page number.
  - Volume 1, 1853-1882. (Reel 1)
  - Volume 2, 1883-1888.
  - Volume 3, 1889-1892. (Reel 2)
  - Volume 4, 1893-1895.
  - Volume 5, 1896-1900. (Reel 3)
  - Volume 6, 1901-1905.
  - Volume 7, 1906-1909. (Reel 4)
  - Volume 8, 1910-1913.
  - Volume 9, 1914-1915. (Reel 5)
  - Volume 10, 1916-1917.
  - Volume 11, 1918-1919. (Reel 6)
  - Volume 12, 1920-1921.
  - Volume 13, 1922-1923. (Reel 7)
  - Volume 14, 1924-1925.
  - Volume 15, 1926-1928. (Reel 8)
  - Volume 16, 1929-1930.
  - Volume 17, 1931-1933. (Reel 9)
  - Volume 18, 1934-1936.
  - Volume 19, 1937-1939. (Reel 10)
  - Volume 20, 1940-1942.
  - Volume 21, 1942-1944. (Reel 11)
  - Volume 22, 1945-1946.
  - Volume 23, 1947-1948. (Reel 12)
  - Volume 24, 1949-1950.
  - Volume 25, 1951-1952. (Reel 13)
  - Volume 26, 1953-1954.
  - Volume 27, 1955-1956. (Reel 14)
  - Volume 28, 1957-1958.
  - Volume 29, 1959-1960. (Reel 15)
  - Volume 30, 1961-1962.
  - Volume 31, 1963-1964. (Reel 16)
  - Volume 32, 1965-1966.
  - Volume 33, 1967-1968. (Reel 17)
  - Volume 34, 1969. (Reel 18)
  - Volume 35, 1970. (Reel 19)
  - Volume 36, 1971-1972.
  - Volume 37, 1973. (Reel 20)
  - Volume 38, 1974. (Reel 21)
  - Volume 39, 1975. (Reel 22)
  - Volume 40, 1976. (Reel 23)
  - Volume 41, 1977. (Reel 24)
  - Volume 42, 1978. (Reel 25)
  - Volume 43, 1979. (Reel 26)
  - Volume 44, 1980. (Reel 27)
  - Volume 45, 1981. (Reel 28)
  - Volume 46, 1982. (Reel 29)
  - Volume 47, 1983-1985. (Reel 30)
  - 1986-1989. (Reel 31)
- Marriage Certificates, 1853-1996.
  Numerical listing of marriage certificates; on rolls with more than one volume, the volumes may appear in reverse numerical order.
  - Volumes 1-4, 1853-1868. (Reel 1)
  - Volumes 5-8, 1868-1873. (Reel 2)
  - Volumes 9-12, 1873-1878. (Reel 3)
  - Volumes 13-16, 1878-1880. (Reel 4)
  - Volumes 17-20, 1881-1882. (Reel 5)
  - Volumes 21-24, 1883-1884. (Reel 6)
  - Volumes 25-28, 1884-1885. (Reel 7)
  - Volumes 29-32, 1885-1886. (Reel 8)
  - Volumes 33-36, 1886-1887. (Reel 9)
  - Volumes 37-40, 1887-1888. (Reel 10)
  - Volumes 41-44, 1888-1889. (Reel 11)
  - Volumes 45-48, 1890. (Reel 12)
  - Volumes 49-52, 1890-1891. (Reel 13)
  - Volumes 53-56, 1891-1892. (Reel 14)
  - Volumes 57-60, 1892-1894. (Reel 15)
  - Volumes 61-64, 1893-1894. (Reel 16)
  - Volumes 65-68, 1894-1895. (Reel 17)
  - Volumes 69-72, 1895-1897. (Reel 18)
  - Volumes 73-76, 1897-1898. (Reel 19)
  - Volumes 77-80, 1898-1899. (Reel 20)
  - Volumes 81-84, 1899-1900. (Reel 21)
  - Volumes 85-88, 1900-1901. (Reel 22)
  - Volumes 89-92, 1901-1902. (Reel 23)
  - Volumes 93-96, 1902. (Reel 24)
  - Volumes 97-100, 1902-1903. (Reel 25)
  - Volumes 101-104, 1903-1904. (Reel 26)
  - Volumes 105-108, 1904-1905. (Reel 27)
  - Volumes 109-112, 1905. (Reel 28)
  - Volumes 113-116, 1905-1906. (Reel 29)
  - Volumes 117-120, 1906-1907. (Reel 30)
  - Volumes 121-124, 1906-1906. (Reel 31)
  - Volumes 125-128, 1908. (Reel 32)
  - Volumes 129-132, 1908-1909. (Reel 33)
  - Volumes 133-136, 1908-1909. (Reel 34)
  - Volumes 137-140, 1909-1910. (Reel 35)
  - Volumes 141-144, 1910-1911. (Reel 36)
  - Volumes 145-148, 1910-1911. (Reel 37)
  - Volumes 149-152, 1911. (Reel 38)
  - Volumes 153-156, 1911-1912. (Reel 39)
  - Volumes 157-160, 1912-1913. (Reel 40)
  - Volumes 161-164, 1912-1913. (Reel 41)
  - Volumes 165-168, 1913. (Reel 42)
  - Volumes 169-172, 1913-1914. (Reel 43)
  - Volumes 173-176, 1914. (Reel 44)
  - Volumes 177-180, 1914-1915. (Reel 45)
  - Volumes 181-184, 1915. (Reel 46)
  - Volumes 185-188, 1915. (Reel 47)
  - Volumes 189-192, 1915-1916. (Reel 48)
  - Volumes 193-196, 1916. (Reel 49)
  - Volumes 197-200, 1916-1917. (Reel 50)
  - Volumes 201-204, 1917. (Reel 51)
  - Volumes 205-208, 1917-1918. (Reel 52)
  - Volumes 209-212, 1917-1918. (Reel 53)
  - Volumes 213-216, 1918. (Reel 54)
  - Volumes 217-220, 1918-1919. (Reel 55)
  - Volumes 221-224, 1919. (Reel 56)
  - Volumes 225-228, 1919. (Reel 57)
  - Volumes 229-232, 1919-1920. (Reel 58)
  - Volumes 233-236, 1920. (Reel 59)
  - Volumes 237-240, 1920. (Reel 60)
  - Volumes 241-244, 1920-1921. (Reel 61)
  - Volumes 245-248, 1921. (Reel 62)
  - Volumes 249-252, 1921. (Reel 63)
  - Volumes 253-256, 1921-1922. (Reel 64)
  - Volumes 257-260, 1922. (Reel 65)
  - Volumes 261-264, 1922. (Reel 66)
  - Volumes 265-268, 1922-1923. (Reel 67)
  - Volumes 269-272, 1923. (Reel 68)
  - Volumes 273-276, 1923-1924. (Reel 69)
  - Volumes 277-280, 1923-1924. (Reel 70)
  - Volumes 281-284, 1924. (Reel 71)
  - Volumes 285-288, 1924-1925. (Reel 72)
  - Volumes 289-292, 1925. (Reel 73)
  - Volumes 293-296, 1925. (Reel 74)
  - Volumes 297-300, 1925-1926. (Reel 75)
  - Volumes 301-304, 1926. (Reel 76)
  - Volumes 301, 305-308, 1926-1927. (Reel 77)
  - Volumes 309-312, 1926-1927. (Reel 78)
  - Volumes 313-316, 1927. (Reel 79)
  - Volumes 317-320, 1927-1928. (Reel 80)
  - Volumes 321-324, 1928. (Reel 81)
  - Volumes 325-328, 1928-1929. (Reel 82)
  - Volumes 329-332, 1928. (Reel 83)
  - Volumes 333-336, 1929. (Reel 84)
  - Volumes 337-340, 1929-1930. (Reel 85)
  - Volumes 341-344, 1930. (Reel 86)
  - Volumes 345-348, 1930-1931. (Reel 87)
  - Volumes 349-352, 1931. (Reel 88)
  - Volumes 353-356, 1931-1932. (Reel 89)
  - Volumes 357-360, 1932. (Reel 90)
  - Volumes 361-364, 1932-1933. (Reel 91)
  - Volumes 365-368, 1933. (Reel 92)
  - Volumes 369-372, 1933-1934. (Reel 93)
  - Volumes 373-376, 1934-1935. (Reel 94)
  - Volumes 377-380, 1934-1935. (Reel 95)
  - Volumes 381-384, 1935. (Reel 96)
  - Volumes 385-388, 1935-1936. (Reel 97)
  - Volumes 389-392, 1935-1936. (Reel 98)
  - Volumes 393-396, 1936. (Reel 99)
  - Volumes 397-400, 1936-1938. (Reel 100)
  - Volumes 401-404, 1937. (Reel 101)
  - Volumes 405-408, 1937. (Reel 102)
  - Volumes 409-412, 1937-1938. (Reel 103)
  - Volumes 413-416, 1938. (Reel 104)
  - Volumes 417-420, 1938-1939. (Reel 105)
  - Volumes 421-424, 1939. (Reel 106)
  - Volumes 425-428, 1939-1940. (Reel 107)
  - Volumes 429-432, 1939-1940. (Reel 108)
  - Volumes 433-436, 1940. (Reel 109)
  - Volumes 437-440, 1940-1941. (Reel 110)
  - Volumes 441-444, 1941. (Reel 111)
  - Volumes 445-448, 1941. (Reel 112)
  - Volumes 449-452, 1941. (Reel 113)
  - Volumes 453-456, 1941-1942. (Reel 114)
  - Volumes 457-460, 1942. (Reel 115)
  - Volumes 461-464, 1942. (Reel 116)
  - Volumes 465-468, 1942-1943. (Reel 117)
  - Volumes 469-472, 1943-1943. (Reel 118)
  - Volumes 473-476, 1943. (Reel 119)
  - Volumes 477-480, 1943-1944. (Reel 120)
  - Volumes 481-484, 1944. (Reel 121)
  - Volumes 485-488, 1944. (Reel 122)
  - Volumes 489-492, 1944-1945. (Reel 123)
  - Volumes 493-496, 1945. (Reel 124)
  - Volumes 497-500, 1945. (Reel 125)
  - Volumes 501-504, 1945-1946. (Reel 126)
  - Volumes 505-508, 1946. (Reel 127)
  - Volumes 509-512, 1946. (Reel 128)
  - Volumes 513-516, 1946. (Reel 129)
  - Volumes 517-520, 1946. (Reel 130)
  - Volumes 521-524, 1946-1947. (Reel 131)
  - Volumes 525-528, 1947. (Reel 132)
  - Volumes 529-532, 1947. (Reel 133)
  - Volumes 533-536, 1947. (Reel 134)
  - Volumes 537-540, 1947-1948. (Reel 135)
  - Volumes 541-544, 1947-1948. (Reel 136)
  - Volumes 545-548, 1948. (Reel 137)
  - Volumes 549-552, 1948. (Reel 138)
  - Volumes 553-556, 1948. (Reel 139)
  - Volumes 557-560, 1948-1949. (Reel 140)
  - Volumes 561-564, 1949. (Reel 141)
  - Volumes 565-568, 1949. (Reel 142)
  - Volumes 569-572, 1949. (Reel 143)
  - Volumes 573-576, 1949-1950. (Reel 144)
  - Volumes 577-580, 1950. (Reel 145)
  - Volumes 581-584, 1950. (Reel 146)
  - Volumes 585-588, 1950-1951. (Reel 147)
  - Volumes 589-592, 1951. (Reel 148)
  - Volumes 593-595, 1951. (Reel 149)
  - Volumes 596-599, 1951-1952. (Reel 150)
  - Volumes 600-603, 1951-1952. (Reel 151)
  - Volumes 604-607, 1952. (Reel 152)
  - Volumes 608-611, 1952. (Reel 153)
  - Volumes 612-615, 1952-1953. (Reel 154)
  - Volumes 616-619, 1953. (Reel 155)
  - Volumes 620-623, 1953. (Reel 156)
  - Volumes 624-627, 1953-1954. (Reel 157)
  - Volumes 628-631, 1954. (Reel 158)
  - Volumes 632-635, 1954. (Reel 159)
  - Volumes 636-639, 1954-1955. (Reel 160)
  - Volumes 640-643, 1955. (Reel 161)
  - Volumes 644-647, 1955. (Reel 162)
  - Volumes 648-651, 1955-1956. (Reel 163)
  - Volumes 652-655, 1956. (Reel 164)
  - Volumes 656-659, 1956. (Reel 165)
  - Volumes 660-663, 1956-1957. (Reel 166)
  - Volumes 664-667, 1957. (Reel 167)
  - Volumes 668-671, 1957. (Reel 168)
  - Volumes 672-675, 1957-1958. (Reel 169)
  - Volumes 676-679, 1958. (Reel 170)
  - Volumes 680-682, 1958. (Reel 171)
  - Volumes 683-685, 1958-1959. (Reel 172)
  - Volumes 686-688, 1959. (Reel 173)
  - Volumes 689-691, 1959. (Reel 174)
  - Volumes 692-694, 1959-1960. (Reel 175)
  - Volumes 695-697 (December 1959), 1959-1960. (Reel 176)
  - Volumes 698-700, 1960. (Reel 177)
  - Volumes 701-703, 1960. (Reel 178)
  - Volumes 704-706, 1960. (Reel 179)
  - Volumes 707-709, 1960-1961. (Reel 180)
  - Volumes 710-712, 1960-1961. (Reel 181)
  - Volumes 713-715, 1961. (Reel 182)
  - Volumes 716-718, 1961. (Reel 183)
  - Volumes 719-721, 1961. (Reel 184)
  - Volumes 722-724, 1961-1962. (Reel 185)
  - Volumes 725-727, 1962. (Reel 186)
  - Volumes 728-730, 1962. (Reel 187)
  - Volumes 731-733, 1962. (Reel 188)
  - Volumes 734-736, 1962-1963. (Reel 189)
  - Volumes 737-739, 1963. (Reel 190)
  - Volumes 740-742, 1963. (Reel 191)
  - Volumes 743-745, 1963. (Reel 192)
  - Volumes 746-748, 1963. (Reel 193)
  - Volumes 749-751, 1963-1964. (Reel 194)
  - Volumes 752-754, 1964. (Reel 195)
  - Volumes 755-757, 1964. (Reel 196)
  - Volumes 758-760, 1964. (Reel 197)
  - Volumes 761-763, 1964. (Reel 198)
  - Volumes 764-766, 1964-1965. (Reel 199)
  - Volumes 767-769, 1965. (Reel 200)
  - Volumes 770-772, 1965. (Reel 201)
  - Volumes 773-775, 1965-1966. (Reel 202)
  - Volumes 776-778, 1965. (Reel 203)
  - Volumes 779-781, 1965-1966. (Reel 204)
  - Volumes 782-784, 1966. (Reel 205)
  - Volumes 785-787, 1966. (Reel 206)
  - Volumes 788-790, 1966. (Reel 207)
  - Volumes 791-793, 1966. (Reel 208)
  - Volumes 794-796, 1966. (Reel 209)
  - Volumes 797-799, 1966-1967. (Reel 210)
  - Volumes 800-802, 1967. (Reel 211)
  - Volumes 803-805, 1967. (Reel 212)
  - Volumes 806-808, 1967. (Reel 213)
  - Volumes 809-811, 1967. (Reel 214)
  - Volumes 812-814, 1967. (Reel 215)
  - Volumes 815-816, 1967-1968. (Reel 216)
  - Volume 817, 1968. (Reel 217)
  - Volume 818, 1968. (Reel 218)
  - Volume 819, 1968. (Reel 219)
  - Volume 820, 1968-1969. (Reel 220)
  - Volume 821, 1968-1969. (Reel 221)
  - Volume 822, 1969. (Reel 222)
  - Volume 823, 1969. (Reel 223)
  - Volume 824, 1969. (Reel 224)
  - Volume 825, 1969-1970. (Reel 225)
  - Volume 826, 1969-1970. (Reel 226)
  - Volume 827, 1970. (Reel 227)
  - Volume 828, 1970. (Reel 228)
  - Volume 829, 1970. (Reel 229)
  - Volume 830, 1970. (Reel 230)
  - Volume 831, 1970-1971. (Reel 231)
  - Volume 832, 1971. (Reel 232)
  - Volume 833, 1971. (Reel 233)
  - Volume 834, 1971. (Reel 234)
  - Volume 835, 1971-1972. (Reel 235)
  - Volume 836, 1972. (Reel 236)
  - Volume 837, 1972-1973. (Reel 237)
  - Volume 838, 1972-1973. (Reel 238)
  - Volume 839, 1972. (Reel 239)
  - Volume 840, 1972-1973. (Reel 240)
  - Volume 841, 1973. (Reel 241)
  - Volume 842, 1973. (Reel 242)
  - Volume 843, 1973. (Reel 243)
  - Volume 844, 1973-1974. (Reel 244)
  - Volume 845, 1973-1974. (Reel 245)
  - Volume 846, 1973-1974. (Reel 246)
  - Volume 847, 1974. (Reel 247)
  - Volume 848, 1974-1975. (Reel 248)
  - Volume 849, 1974-1975. (Reel 249)
  - Volume 850, 1974-1975. (Reel 250)
  - Volume 851, 1975-1976. (Reel 251)
  - Volume 852, 1975. (Reel 252)
  - Volume 853, 1975-1976. (Reel 253)
  - Volume 854, 1976. (Reel 254)
  - Volume 855, 1976. (Reel 255)
  - Volume 856, 1976-1977. (Reel 256)
  - Volume 857, 1976. (Reel 257)
  - Volume 858, 1976-1977. (Reel 258)
  - Volume 859, 1976-1978. (Reel 259)
  - Volume 860, 1977. (Reel 260)
  - Volume 861, 1977-1978. (Reel 261)
  - Volume 862, 1977-1978. (Reel 262)
  - Volume 863, 1977-1978. (Reel 263)
  - Volume 864, 1977-1978. (Reel 264)
  - Volume 865, 1978. (Reel 265)
  - Volume 866, 1978-1979. (Reel 266)
  - Volume 867, 1978-1979. (Reel 267)
  - Volume 868, 1979. (Reel 268)
  - Volume 869, 1979. (Reel 269)
  - Volume 870, 1979. (Reel 270)
  - Volume 871, 1979-1980. (Reel 271)
  - Volume 872, 1979-1980. (Reel 272)
  - Volume 873, 1979-1980. (Reel 273)
  - Volume 874, 1979-1980. (Reel 274)
  - Volume 875, 1980. (Reel 275)
  - Volume 876, 1980-1981. (Reel 276)
  - Volume 877, 1980-1981. (Reel 277)
  - Volume 878, 1980-1981. (Reel 278)
  - Volume 879, 1980-1981. (Reel 279)
  - Volume 880, 1981. (Reel 280)
  - Volume 881, 1981. (Reel 281)
  - Volume 882, 1981-1982. (Reel 282)
  - Volume 883, 1981-1982. (Reel 283)
  - Volume 884, 1981-1982. (Reel 284)
  - Volume 885, 1981-1983. (Reel 285)
  - Volume 886, 1981-1982. (Reel 286)
  - Volume 887, 1982. (Reel 287)
  - Volume 888, 1982-1983. (Reel 288)
  - Volume 889, 1982-1983. (Reel 289)
  - Volume 890, 1982-1983. (Reel 290)
  - Volume 891, 1982-1983. (Reel 291)
  - Volume 892, 1982-1983. (Reel 292)
  - Volume 893, 1983. (Reel 293)
  - Volume 894, 1983. (Reel 294)
  - Volume 895, 1983-1984. (Reel 295)
  - Volume 896, 1983-1984. (Reel 296)
  - Volume 897, 1983-1984. (Reel 297)
  - Volume 898, 1983-1984. (Reel 298)
  - Volume 899, 1984. (Reel 299)
  - Volume 900, 1984-1985. (Reel 300)
  - Volume 901, 1984-1985. (Reel 301)
  - Volume 902, 1984-1985. (Reel 302)
  - Volume 903, 1984-1985. (Reel 303)
  - Volume 904, 1985. (Reel 304)
  - Volume 905, 1985-1986. (Reel 305)
  - Volume 906, 1985-1986. (Reel 306)
  - Volume 907, 1985-1986. (Reel 307)
  - Volume 908, 1985-1986. (Reel 308)
  - Volume 909, 1986. (Reel 309)
  - Volume 910, 1986. (Reel 310)
  - Volume 911, 1986-1987. (Reel 311)
  - Volume 912, 1986-1987. (Reel 312)
  - Volume 913, 1986-1987. (Reel 313)
  - Volume 914, 1986-1987. (Reel 314)
  - Volume 915, 1987. (Reel 315)
  - Volume 916, 1987-1988. (Reel 316)
  - Volume 917, 1987-1988.. (Reel 317)
  - Volume 918, 1987-1988.. (Reel 318)
  - Volume 919, 1987-1988. (Reel 319)
  - Volume 920, 1987-1988. (Reel 320)
  - Volume 921, 1988-1989. (Reel 321)
  - Volume 922, 1988-1989. (Reel 322)
  - Volume 923, 1988-1989. (Reel 323)
  - Volume 924, 1988-1989. (Reel 324)
  - Volume 925, 1988-1989. (Reel 325)
  - Volumes 926-927, 1988-1989. (Reel 326)
  - Volume 928, 1989-1990. (Reel 327)
  - Volume 929, 1989-1990. (Reel 328)
  - Volume 930, 1989-1990. (Reel 329)
  - Volume 931, 1990. (Reel 330)
  - Volume 932, 1990. (Reel 331)
  - Volume 933, 1990-1991. (Reel 332)
  - Volume 934, 1990-1991. (Reel 333)
  - Volume 935, 1990-1991. (Reel 334)
  - Volume 936, 1991. (Reel 335)
  - Volume 937, 1991. (Reel 336)
  - Volume 938, 1991. (Reel 337)
  - Volume 939, 1991-1992. (Reel 338)
  - Volume 940, 1991-1992. (Reel 339)
  - Volume 941, 1992. (Reel 340)
  - Volume 942, 1992. (Reel 341)
  - Volume 943, 1992-1993. (Reel 342)
  - Volume 944, 1992-1993. (Reel 343)
  - Volume 945, 1993. (Reel 344)
  - Volume 946, 1993. (Reel 345)
  - Volume 947, 1993-1994. (Reel 346)
  - Volume 948, 1993-1994. (Reel 347)
  - Volume 949, 1994. (Reel 348)
  - Volume 950, 1994. (Reel 349)
  - Volume 951, 1994. (Reel 350)
  - Volume 952, 1994-1995. (Reel 351)
  - Volume 953, 1994-1995. (Reel 352)
  - Volume 954, 1995. (Reel 353)
  - Volume 955, 1995. (Reel 354)
  - Volume 956, 1995-1996. (Reel 355)
  - Volume 957, 1995-1996. (Reel 356)
  - Volume 958, 1995-1996. (Reel 357)
  - Volume 959, 1996. (Reel 358)
  - Volume 960, 1996. (Reel 359)
  - Volume 961, 1996-1997. (Reel 360)
  - Volume 962, 1996-1997. (Reel 361)
  - Volume 963, 1997. (Reel 362)
  - Volume 964, 1997. (Reel 363)
  - Volume 965, 1997. (Reel 364)
  - Volume 966, 1997. (Reel 365)
  - Volume 967, 1997-1998. (Reel 366)
- Birth Certificate Index, ca. 1870-1931.
  Alphabetical listing by surname.
  - ca. 1870-ca. 1910. (Reel 1)
    At the beginning of each letter of the alphabet, supplemental births for the years 1876, 1878, and 1881 are listed.
  - Volume 1, ca. 1890-1920. (Reel 2)
  - Volume 2, 1920-1931.
- Birth Certificates, 1866-1902.
  Numerical listing of birth certificates.
  - Reels 1-6: Hennepin County (does not include the City of Minneapolis), 1870-1902.
    - 1870-1879. (Reel 1)
    - 1880-1883. (Reel 2)
    - 1884-1887. (Reel 3)
    - 1888-1892. (Reel 4)
    - 1893-1897. (Reel 5)
    - 1898-1902. (Reel 6)
  - Reels 7-50: City of Minneapolis, 1866-1900.
    Many of the earlier dated records appear to be delayed birth certificates.
    - December 17, 1866-December 10, 1885. (Reel 7)
    - January 2, 1886-December 30, 1887. (Reel 8)
    - January-April 1888. (Reel 9)
    - May-August 1888. (Reel 10)
    - September-December 1888. (Reel 11)
    - January-April 1889. (Reel 12)
    - May-August 1889. (Reel 13)
    - September-December 1889. (Reel 14)
    - January-April 1890. (Reel 15)
    - May-August 1890. (Reel 16)
    - September-December 1890. (Reel 17)
    - January-April 1891. (Reel 18)
    - May-August 1891. (Reel 19)
    - September-December 1891. (Reel 20)
    - January-April 1892. (Reel 21)
    - May-August 1892. (Reel 22)
    - September-December 1892. (Reel 23)
    - January-April 1893. (Reel 24)
    - May-August 1893. (Reel 25)
    - September-December 1893. (Reel 26)
    - January-April 1894. (Reel 27)
    - May-August 1894. (Reel 28)
    - September-December 1894. (Reel 29)
    - January-April 1895. (Reel 30)
    - May-August 1895. (Reel 31)
    - September-December 1895. (Reel 32)
    - January-April 1896. (Reel 33)
    - May-August 1896. (Reel 34)
    - September-December 1896. (Reel 35)
    - January-April 1897. (Reel 36)
    - May-August 1897. (Reel 37)
    - September-December 1897. (Reel 38)
    - January-April 1898. (Reel 39)
    - May-August 1898. (Reel 40)
    - September-December 1898. (Reel 41)
    - January-April 1899. (Reel 42)
    - May-August 1899. (Reel 43)
    - September-December 1899. (Reel 44)
    - January-February 1900. (Reel 45)
    - March-April 1900. (Reel 46)
    - May-June 1900. (Reel 47)
    - July-August 1900. (Reel 48)
    - September-October 1900. (Reel 49)
    - November-December 1900. (Reel 50)
- Death Certificate Index, 1890-1931.
  - 1890-1919. (Reel 1)
  - Volume 2, 1920-1931.
- Death Certificates, 1870-1909.
  Numerical listing of death certificates.
  - Reels 1-5: Hennepin County (does not include the City of Minneapolis), 1870-1909.
    - 1870-1879. (Reel 1)
    - 1880-1889. (Reel 2)
    - 1890-1899. (Reel 3)
    - 1900-1907. (Reel 4)
    - 1908-1909. (Reel 5)
  - Reels 6-47: City of Minneapolis, 1870-1908.
    Many of the earlier dated records appear to be delayed death certificates.
    - 1870-1875. (Reel 6)
    - 1876-1879. (Reel 7)
    - 1880-1881. (Reel 8)
    - 1882. (Reel 9)
    - 1883. (Reel 10)
    - 1884. (Reel 11)
    - 1885. (Reel 12)
    - 1886. (Reel 13)
    - January-October 16, 1888. (Reel 14)
    - October 17-December 1888. (Reel 15)
    - 1889. (Reel 16)
    - 1890. (Reel 17)
    - 1891. (Reel 18)
    - January-December 16, 1892. (Reel 19)
    - December 16-31, 1892. (Reel 20)
    - 1893. (Reel 21)
    - 1894. (Reel 22)
    - 1895. (Reel 23)
    - 1896. (Reel 24)
    - September-December 1897. (Reel 25)
    - 1898. (Reel 26)
    - 1899. (Reel 27)
    - 1900. (Reel 28)
    - January-November 1901. (Reel 29)
    - December 1901. (Reel 30)
    - 1902. (Reel 31)
    - January-September 1903. (Reel 32)
    - January-April 1904. (Reel 33)
    - May-August 1904. (Reel 34)
    - September-December 1904. (Reel 35)
    - January-April 1905. (Reel 36)
    - May-August 1905. (Reel 37)
    - September-December 1905. (Reel 38)
    - January-April 1906. (Reel 39)
    - May-August 1906. (Reel 40)
    - September-December 1906. (Reel 41)
    - January-April 1907. (Reel 42)
    - May-August 1907. (Reel 43)
    - September-December 1907. (Reel 44)
    - January-April 1908. (Reel 45)
    - May-August 1908. (Reel 46)
    - September-December 1908. (Reel 47)